Arthur Tkachenko

Chief technical officer



(+380) 50 648 13 34



https://www.linkedin.com/in/arthurtkachenko/





arthur.tkachenko.netweight@gmail.com

Tech leader with experience in different areas. Consulting teams of different sizes and company stages. Have a vast knowledge of building and maintaining tech projects. Able to form and scale development teams. During six years lifespan, completed over 20 detailed specifications for US-based startups.



Experience

Jan 2022 - present

commanda group

Product Owner

Managing B2B marketplace development

Feb 2021 - present

LLazyEmail Company

Advisor, GrowthHacker

Tech Infrastructure for email marketing teams

Dec 2021 - present

Dev.to Self-employed

Contributing Writer

https://dev.to/atherdon

Aug 2019 - Jul 2021

Hacker Noon

Software Development Editor

During two years period, reviewed and published most of the articles related to software

engineering. In total published ~50 articles per week x 52 weeks x 2 years

Jun 2017 - present

Groceristar Company

Founder

Solutions for FoodTech startups

2012 - 2016

netWeight Company

Co-Founder

Responsible for project management



Skills

Software Development Project Management **Business Development Technical Recruiting Business Strategy** Team Management Team Leadership



Education

NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERCITY OF UKRAINE "NURE" 2010

Engineer's Degree Software Development



AngelList:

https://angel.co/u/arthur-tkachenko

Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100001542389090

Hackernoon:

https://hackernoon.com/u/arthur.tkachenko

GitHub:

https://github.com/atherdon

Muchrack profile:

https://muckrack.com/arthur-tkachenko-1



Volunteering

Was running an internship program for students. Selected ~100 students from 2500 requests.

Recorded six coding courses on Udemy and shared them with 8000 students for free.